playhawken.com 2019-05-27

# Privacy Policy - Legal - HAWKEN: War is A Machine - Free-to-Play Mech First-Person-Shooter

Hawken Entertainment, Inc., Inc. and its affiliates ("us," "we," or "Hawken Entertainment, Inc.") take your privacy and security very seriously. When you choose to register with PlayHawken.com, you're entrusting us with something important to you. We're going to work hard to make sure that your information stays safe and private. The gist of this policy is to confirm that we collect your personal information, that we'll be very careful with it, and that if somebody tries to mess with us or you, we can take action to stop it and make sure it doesn't happen again.

If anything on this page makes you twitchy, drop us a line at [privacy@playhawken.com](mailto:privacy@playhawken.com) and we'll do whatever we can to improve the situation.

##### Guidelines

We embrace the privacy guidelines as developed by the Online Privacy Alliance and the Federal Trade Commission, and this privacy policy adheres to the principles addressed in those guidelines. To view these guidelines, please visit the web sites of the corresponding organization. 

##### Collection and use of non-personal information

We collect non-personally-identifiable (anonymous) information about you, including the following:

  * Your IP address (a unique number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web; many Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address).
  * Your "top level" domain (i.e., .com, .net, .edu, etc.).
  * Standard information included with every communication sent on the Internet, such as browser type, operating system, browser type and language, service provider, the server your computer is logged into, and local time.
  * We collect data from the Web logs of the servers that deliver this website's content. This includes information about what you view. Along with information gathered from our other users, we create "aggregate data" reports that we may disclose to third parties. We may also study aggregate data in order to enhance our existing services or develop new services.

We will not disclose any personal information to a third party without your express prior written authorization, as described under 'Collection of personal information' below. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our terms of use or to protect our service, site, customers, or others.

##### Use of cookies

This website uses cookies. Cookies are used for record keeping, to track your movements when you visit this website and to help us determine what type of information to present to you. The use of cookies is an industry standard - you'll find them used by most websites. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and do not damage or alter your computer's system files in any way. The first time you visit this website you will be assigned a unique, anonymous ID, which is stored in our cookies on your computer.

##### Collection of personal information

As we roll out new features to playhawken.com, you will need to register in order to use many of them. We will, and you expressly authorize us to, use the information you provide for the purposes identified to you when you registered, including to: 

  * provide and administer this website;
  * communicate with you about services, features, products, special offers, and unique content available through this website or otherwise from Hawken Entertainment, Inc. or about other topics related to Hawken Entertainment, Inc.; products and services that we think you might find of interest; and
  * communicate with you about other products or services we offer.

The only information we provide to other users is that which you elect to share with them. We do not otherwise share this information with other users of this website or with other parties. We never use or share personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the those described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

##### Who is collecting your information

Your information is being collected solely by us. See the discussion under "With whom your information may be shared" below concerning the circumstances under which certain of your information may be disclosed to third parties.

##### With whom your information may be shared

We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. As discussed above under "Collection and use of non-personal information," we may provide aggregate statistics about our users, traffic patterns and related site information to third parties or for other marketing and promotional purposes. In these situations, we would not disclose any information that could be used to personally identify you.

##### How you can have your information removed or corrected

You may have your personally-identifiable information removed from our database at any time by contacting privacy@playhawken.com and requesting that it be removed. To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity before correcting or removing your information. Your personally-identifiable information may be retained for an indefinite time unless you opt to have it removed.

##### Confidentiality and security

We have implemented generally accepted standards of technology security in order to protect information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Access to the information we collect is given only to our employees and to certain independent contractors and agents who need to have access to the information in order to develop, operate, and maintain the website and associated products. These employees and independent contractors are made aware of and required to comply with our privacy policy.

##### Links to other sites

This website may provide links to external websites. When you click on such a link, you will leave this website, at which point the privacy policy of the external website will be in effect, not our policy. We do not control or endorse any external site or its privacy policy in any way. Our policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet and will not be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. We do not control cookies from the other sites that you may link to from this website.

##### Children

Neither this website nor any service it may provide, market, or advertise is targeted at or directed to children under 13 years of age, and our content and other services are not written, intended, or designed for children under the age of 13. To ensure that we stay in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we review the details of COPPA on a regular basis.

##### Changes to this privacy policy

All versions of this privacy policy are dated with the effective date (the date on which the policy was posted to this website). We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to this Privacy Policy to this website, in which case you will be provided the opportunity to review the new privacy policy and required to agree to its terms and conditions or cease using this website. We will only use the information we learn about you in the manner described in the privacy policy in effect when the information was collected from you or that you later agree to.

##### Changes in corporate structure

If Hawken Entertainment, Inc. is sold, merged or otherwise transferred to another entity, the personal information you have provided to us may be transferred as part of that transaction. However, we will take steps to assure that any personal information is used in a manner consistent with the privacy policy under which it was collected.

##### Effect of legal obligations upon this privacy policy

We may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that its disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

##### Effect of privacy policy

This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. As noted above, we may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time in our sole discretion.

##### Security issues

If you are a user of this website and have a concern regarding the security of your account or personally-identifiable information, have found a security vulnerability in this website or have a security incident to report, please, please contact Hawken Entertainment, Inc. via email at security@playhawken.com or via postal mail sent to: 16787 Beach Blvd. #465 Huntington Beach, CA 92647 or via telephone at (949) 486-0400. Include a detailed summary of the issue you've discovered. We may reach out to you if we need more information.

_Effective August 5, 2015_
